[
    {
    "ques_no": "1",
        "question":"What is C?",
        "a":"Programming Language",
        "b":"A game",
        "c":"A move",
        "d":"Node of these",
        "correct":"a",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "2",
        "question":"What is the correct format specifier to print an interger in C?",
        "a":"%c",
        "b":"%d",
        "c":"%f",
        "d":"%s",
        "correct":"b",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "3",
        "question":"Which of the following is the correct syntax for the main function in C?",
        "a":"void main()",
        "b":"int main()",
        "c":"main()",
        "d":"All of the above",
        "correct":"b",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "4",
        "question":"Which of the following is used to take input from the user in C?",
        "a":"printf()",
        "b":"cin",
        "c":"scanf()",
        "d":"input()",
        "correct":"c",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "5",
        "question":"Which of following is a correct identifier in c++",
        "a":"2 variable",
        "b":"_value",
        "c":"first-name",
        "d":"class",
        "correct":"b",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "6",
        "question":"Which of the following is used to create an object in c++",
        "a":"class",
        "b":"struct",
        "c":"new",
        "d":"object",
        "correct":"c",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "7",
        "question":"What is the size of an int in c++(most 32-bit system)?",
        "a":"2 bytes",
        "b":"4 bytes",
        "c":"8 bytes",
        "d":"Depends on the compiler",
        "correct":"b",
        "answer":"e"
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "8",
        "question":"Which of the following is the correct syntax of c++ comment?",
        "a":"/*comment*/",
        "b":"//comment",
        "c":"Both A and B",
        "d":"# comment",
        "correct":"c",
        "answer":"e"
        
    },
    {
        "ques_no": "9",
        "question":"What is the return type of a constructor?",
        "a":"int",
        "b":"void",
        "c":"class name",
        "d":"it has no return type",
        "correct":"d",
        "answer":"e"
        

    },
    {
        "ques_no": "10",
        "question":"Which keyword is used to define a class in c++?",
        "a":"object",
        "b":"structure",
        "c":"class",
        "d":"define",
        "correct":"c",
        "answer":"e"
        
    }
]